gayforit.eu 2018-12-23

# GayForIt - Free Gay Porn Videos

Privacy policy for www.gayforit.eu

Do you need to register with the ICO? - ICO Data Protection Register Self Assessment  
Online checklist tools to help you comply with the GDPR - Data Protection Self Assessment Toolkit  
Determine your Lawful Basis for processing - Lawful Basis Interactive Guidance Tool  
Privacy Policy Notice  
The policy: This privacy policy notice is for this website; [www.gayforit.eu] and served by GF Networks Limited, 34 New House, 67-68 Hatton Garden London EC1N  
8JY and governs the privacy of those who use it. The purpose of this policy is to explain to you how we control, process, handle and protect your   
personal information while browsing or using this website, including your rights under current laws and regulations. If you do not agree to the following   
policy you may wish to cease viewing / using this website.   
Policy key definitions:

"I", "our", "us", or "we" refer to the business, www.gayforit.eu.  
"you", "the user" refer to the person(s) using this website.  
GDPR means General Data Protection Act.  
PECR means Privacy & Electronic Communications Regulation.  
ICO means Information Commissioner's Office.  
Cookies mean small files stored on a users computer or device.  
Processing of your personal data  
Under the GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation) we control and / or process any personal information about you electronically using the following lawful   
bases.  
We are exempt from registration in the ICO Data Protection Register because our data is not held in the UK.  
Lawful basis: Consent  
We process your information in the following ways: Storage in database if a member or via cookies held by customer only.  
Data retention period: We will continue to process your information under this basis until you withdraw consent or it is determined your consent no longer exists.  
Sharing your information: We do not share your information with third parties. / We do share your personal information with third parties and they include; .

We process your information in the following ways: To allow us to provide features on our website and store your preferences.  
Data retention period: Cookies are stored locally, minimal account information is held for 5 years and can be deleted upon request.  
Sharing your information: We do not share your information with third parties. .  
Sharing your information: We do not share your information with third parties. / We do share your personal information with third parties and they include; .  
Your individual rights  
Under the GDPR your rights are as follows. You can read more about your rights in details here;

the right to be informed;  
the right of access;  
the right to rectification;  
the right to erasure;  
the right to restrict processing;  
the right to data portability;  
the right to object; and  
the right not to be subject to automated decision-making including profiling.  
You also have the right to complain to the ICO [www.ico.org.uk] if you feel there is a problem with the way we are handling your data.

We handle subject access requests in accordance with the GDPR.

Internet cookies  
We use cookies on this website to provide you with a better user experience. We do this by placing a small text file on your device / computer hard drive to track   
how you use the website, to record or log whether you have seen particular messages that we display, to keep you logged into the website where applicable,   
to display relevant adverts or content, referred you to a third party website.

Some cookies are required to enjoy and use the full functionality of this website.

We use a cookie control system which allows you to accept the use of cookies, and control which cookies are saved to your device / computer. Some cookies will   
be saved for specific time periods, where others may last indefinitely. Your web browser should provide you with the controls to manage and delete cookies   
from your device, please see your web browser options.

Cookies that we use are;

Session ID and user preferences.  
Data security and protection  
We ensure the security of any personal information we hold by using secure data storage technologies and precise procedures in how we store, access and manage  
that information. Our methods meet the GDPR compliance requirement.

Transparent Privacy Explanations  
We have provided some further explanations about user privacy and the way we use this website to help promote a transparent and honest user privacy   
methodology.

Sponsored links, affiliate tracking & commissions  
Our website may contain adverts, sponsored and affiliate links on some pages. These are typically served through our advertising partners. We only use trusted   
advertising partners who each have high standards of user privacy and security. However we do not control the actual adverts seen / displayed by our  
advertising partners. Our ad partners may collect data and use cookies for ad personalisation and measurement. Where ad preferences are requested as 'non-  
personalised' cookies may still be used for frequency capping, aggregated ad reporting and to combat fraud and abuse.

Clicking on any adverts, sponsored or affiliate links may track your actions by using a cookie saved to your device. You can read more about cookies on this   
website above. Your actions are usually recorded as a referral from our website by this cookie. In most cases we earn a very small commission from the   
advertiser or advertising partner, at no cost to you, whether you make a purchase on their website or not.

We use advertising partners in these ways to help generate an income from the website, which allows us to continue our work and provide you with the best overall  
experience and valued information.

If you have any concerns about this we suggest you do not click on any adverts, sponsored or affiliate links found throughout the website.

Email marketing messages & subscription  
We will only email you directly, we do not sell or allow other parties to contact you. We do not ask for phone numbers therefore we do not SMS.

Email marketing messages that we send may contain tracking beacons / tracked clickable links or similar server technologies in order to track subscriber activity   
within email marketing messages. Where used, such marketing messages may record a range of data such as; times, dates, I.P addresses, opens, clicks,   
forwards, geographic and demographic data. Such data, within its limitations will show the activity each subscriber made for that email campaign.

Any email marketing messages we send are in accordance with the GDPR and the PECR. We provide you with an easy method to withdraw your consent   
(unsubscribe) or manage your preferences / the information we hold about you at any time. See any marketing messages for instructions on how to unsubscribe or  
manage your preferences, you can also unsubscribe from all MailChimp lists, by following this link, otherwise contact the EMS provider.

Email address  
I.P address  
Subscription time & date  
Preferences such as number of videos per page.
